I've found out
that the novel
was written by your wife,
Shen Suhe.
She has been arrested
and will be dealt with
after the investigation.
What?
Your Highness, as per the decree,
you take over the case of Shen Yi and Xiao Wei.
Please cooperate with the Dali Court.
This is impossible!
Your Highness,
do you want to defy the imperial edict?
Lord Minister,
please.
Your Highness, please follow me inside.
Hurry up!
What are you dawdling for?
Move faster!
What are you standing there for?
Go inside!
I have a plan to solve this case.
Your Highness,
are you interested?
You have a plan?
I don't want to
play any childish tricks with you.
Your Highness, you've just returned,
but rumors are already spreading
that you and General Xiao Wei
had a relationship
with my father.
You returned to the capital
to seek justice for them.
I heard
His Majesty intended to
hand over this case to you,
but you refused.
You must have realized
His Majesty
wasn't truly seeking justice,
but testing
your stance on my father's conviction.
Now,
you've brought me here to recover.
I'm afraid this complaint
has already reached His Majesty.
If they keep fabricating stories like this,
it will be very unfavorable
for both Your Highness
and the PM's Residence.
Why not
find a pretext
to imprison me in the imperial prison?
to prove your determination to His Majesty.
Secondly,
it can show the world
that you
are selfless
and have nothing to do
with the PM's Residence.
To set a trap with your own body,
is this your plan?
The prison
is not as simple as you think.
Can a weak girl like you
really handle it?
You don't have to worry about me.
As long as I can save my father,
I'm willing to
risk my life.
Father,
I'll definitely save you this time.
Your Highness,
these
are the case files handed over by Dali Temple.
These two
are the secret letters
that incriminated the PM and Xiao.
It's indeed his handwriting.
I've also
checked Minister Shen's letter.
It's indeed his handwriting.
It seems
that both of them
were under the influence of drugs
when they wrote these secret letters.
Moreover,
I also found out that
His Highness
has set up a secret drug-making point outside the city.
I'm afraid of alarming them,
so I didn't dare to act rashly.
I just sent someone
to secretly monitor their movements.
Where is Prime Minister Shen?
Minister Shen was previously
in the secret prison set up in the Dali Temple.
Now he has been transferred to the prison.
But...
But what?
Eat.
What are you looking at?
Eat or not?
Don't make so much fuss.
Your Highness.
Where is Shen Suhe?
She's inside.
I'll show you the way.
Prince Yu is here.
Your Highness.
You didn't sleep all night.
How is Prince Yu?
Did he take over the case smoothly?
You can see Minister Shen now.
Really?
Thank you, Your Highness.
Wait a moment.
I'll take you to see him now,
but you need to be mentally prepared.
You...
Finish them all.
Yes, yes.
Father.
Father, it's Sui'er.
What happened to my father?
Minister Shen has been poisoned.
Though it hasn't been long,
the dosage was significant,
damaging his heart and
causing mental disorder.
Is it taro powder?
Exactly.
This poison uses taro powder
with other herbs.
At best, it causes hallucinations.
At worst,
it can be lethal.
Is there an antidote?
Your Highness once sent me
this taro powder-based poison.
I have a method to detoxify it,
but
I'm not sure
if it will be effective.
That means
my father can still be saved, right?
I can't guarantee
that I can cure him.
I can only try my best.
How long will it take?
This poison
is much more powerful
than the previous ones.
I have to adjust the prescription
while treating him.
If everything goes well,
he can be cured in one or two months.
But maybe it will take
longer.
One or two months?
Prince,
didn't Your Majesty say you only had seven days?
If no other evidence is found within seven days...
Seven days?
If we can prove that Minister Shen and General Xiao are innocent,
Minister Shen will be dealt with according to the law.
Is there any other way?
I thought
as long as we can find Minister Shen and cure him,
then
the secret letter
will prove that the Second Prince forced him to write.
With the secret medicine-making point we found,
then
the Second Prince forced the loyal general
will be completely confirmed.
But we don't have that much time now.
Father
I'm Sui'er.
I'm here to see you.
Do you really not recognize me?
Father.
Sui'er.
It's me.
I'm Sui'er.
Father, do you recognize me now?
Father.
Your Highness,
in this state, my father
can't prove his innocence.
But if
we can make the Second Prince expose himself,
we can extend the date of the trial.
Do you have a way?
What did you say?
It was you who told me
Shen Yi is mentally unstable.
Even if he is handed over, he is a living dead.
How did he suddenly get better?
I don't know
what method Prince Yu used,
but he regained his sanity overnight.
Now,
Minister Shen is being guarded
by Prince Yu's men.
We can't get close.
I don't know what he said
after he woke up.
Now,
Prince Yu is taking Shen Suhe
to the Prime Minister's Residence.
Prime Minister's Residence?
Shen Yi has been investigating me.
Does he
have other evidence against me?
Come on.
Take people to the Prime Minister's Residence now.
Stop them at all costs.
And
the pharmaceutical factory outside the city
should be destroyed as soon as possible.
Yes.
Prince
The thing father mentioned
is still in the Prime Minister's Residence.
If it's true that
the evidence against the Second Prince is hidden here,
will Your Majesty let him go?
I'm just responsible for the investigation.
As for how to deal with Minister Shen,
it's up to Your Majesty.
If
Minister Shen is really
framed by a villain,
I promise you,
no matter who the murderer is,
I will deal with him fairly.
Let's split up and look for it.
Yes.
Your Highness,
I found it.
The box.
Prince Rui's Mansion.
The Second Prince's men.
Your Highness.
Are you okay?
How's it going?
As we expected.
The Second Prince
heard that Minister Shen woke up
he immediately sent someone
to the secret pharmaceutical site
to destroy the evidence.
I have already arrested those people.
They confessed to making the medicine.
And
they are sure that it is the Second Prince
who is behind it.
They have been taken to the Dali Temple
and are under our control.
It's time to go to the palace.
Damn it!
Your Majesty, please calm down.
How dare he do such a treacherous act!
Your Majesty,
there might be
some misunderstanding about this.
Although
the Second Prince
runs a pharmaceutical workshop privately,
it does not prove
that he poisoned Minister Shen.
I just returned to the capital.
I've heard a lot of rumors.
It is said that the Second Prince
has never got along with Minister Shen.
Maybe
someone took advantage of this to frame him.
It's not impossible.
He secretly built a pharmaceutical workshop to make poison.
If it's not to harm people,
could it be to save people?
This unfilial son
colludes with the censor in every possible way,
and has made many reports,
trying to force me
to appoint him as the Crown Prince sooner.
Does he think I know nothing?
Now,
Shen Yi is not in his right mind,
and the source of that secret letter has not been clarified.
He is eager to have me deal with Shen Yi
and Shen residence.
His ambition is exposed.
Who else
would have the audacity
to plot against the Prime Minister?
Actually,
there's no need to rush to judgment.
We can call the Second Prince here
to clarify the matter.
Perhaps
there's another reason.
Go.
Yes.
Bring this unfilial son here.
I want to interrogate him myself.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I didn't expect that in just a few days,
Prince Yu has cleared the Prime Minister's name.
I entrusted this matter to you,
and it was indeed a wise decision.
I'm flattered, Your Majesty.
To determine if Minister Shen is unrelated to this case,
we need to wait until his condition improves.
Then we'll know.
I humbly request
that you allow Minister Shen
to be released from prison for medical treatment.
Because the conditions in prison are really harsh,
which is not conducive to treatment.
It would be better to let him move into my residence.
First, it's convenient for treatment.
Second, after all, he is a criminal,
and still needs to be strictly guarded.
Granted.
Send my imperial physician to you.
Make sure to cure Prime Minister Shen.
Yes.
What else do you request?
Just say it.
Your Majesty,
I
do have one more request.
This case
can be solved
was all thanks to the assistance
of Prime Minister Shen's daughter,
Shen Suhe.
She was expelled to Lingguo Temple
for reflection.
However,
she left the temple without permission,
I humbly request that Your Majesty,
considering her contribution to the case,
could exempt her from punishment,
and allow her to enter the mansion
to take care of Minister Shen.
Shen Suhe.
His Majesty's oral edict.
Prince Rui, please see His Majesty immediately.
Your Highness.
It's okay.
Chief Eunuch Li.
I wonder why my father suddenly called me.
Is there anything urgent?
Your Highness,
it's all by His Majesty's order.
I'm just following orders.
If you have any questions,
you'd better ask him
in person.
Chief Li, aren't you supposed to take me
to the palace to see my father?
What does this mean?
Your Highness, you may not know.
This time,
it's true that His Majesty summoned you,
but not to the palace,
but to
the Dali Court.
Your Highness,
please.
Your Highness.
Chuchu,
go to the palace now
and beg my mother to save me.
Okay.